<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Servers>

       <ServerGroup Name="7 Years To DIE Survivor" Logo="" Description="">

               <Server Name="Just Die Already Edition" Logo="">

                       <Description>An overhaul vanilla mod for veteran players who find pure vanilla too easy and are seeking a challenge with the vanilla feel. This overhaul mod adds survival that is lacking in the game.

			**This version is even tougher than the Survivalist Version**

			Recommended settings:
			Warrior, Run during the day, No loot respawn, 24 blood moon count, Airdrops weekly.

			- More wild zombie spawns.
			- Slower progression to extend the live of a world to 100+ days.
			- Farming is nerfed so the struggle for food extends to mid game.
			- Less ammo, food and quantity in loot, less resources when mining and harvesting ores/blocks.
			- Economy rebalanced so you won't be swimming in dukes as easily and have to make thoughtful decisions when buying.
			- A Single Player version of the Charismatic Nature perk. (Survival Instinct)
			- Dying has a harsher consequence, retaining debuffs and hunger, etc.
			- And much more!
			***Added the Spencer Mansion (Resident Evil) a Tier 6 quest***
			***You MUST use Nitrogen World Generator and download the supporting file (link below) for it to spawn in your world***


			Full list of changes can be found at the bottom of the List of Changes document.
			For the original changes, and the file for Nitrogen, go here:
			https://community.7daystodie.com/topic/22254-7-years-to-die-survivor-desolate-interloper-exile-survivor-v116-a193/


                       </Description>

                       <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>

                       <SubscriptionLink></SubscriptionLink>

                       <Version>A19.3</Version>

                       <ReleaseNotes/>

                       <Downloads>

                       <Download>https://github.com/Frantic-Dan/Just-Die-Already-Edition</Download>

                 </Downloads>

               </Server>

       </ServerGroup>

</Servers>